Elihu Thomson Papers 1865-1944 Mss.Ms.Coll.74
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional Correspondence, Ca. 1870-1937; 52 boxes; 26 linear feet
  - Harvard University. Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1906-1926; 7 items (Box Series I-19)
  - Harvard University. Office of the President, 1909-1924; 4 items (Box Series I-19)
  - Harvard University. School of Engineering, 1902-1923; 6 items (Box Series I-19)
  - Harvard University. Wolcott Gibbs Memorial Laboratory, 1910-1918; 5 items (Box Series I-19)
  - Harvard University. Zoological Laboratories, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-19)
    G. H. Parker
  - Haskell, William. E., 1913; 4 items (Box Series I-20)
    Esty Organ Company
  - Haskins, Caryl D., 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hassan, M. W., 1892; 2 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Hassard, A. R., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hastings, C. H., 1892-1909; 6 items (Box Series I-20)
    Hastings & Sons Publishing Co.
  - Hatch, [?], 1889; 2 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Hathaway, S., 1887; 2 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Hathorn, Davey & Co., Ltd., 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Haupt, Lewis M., 1901; 2 items (Box Series I-20)
    Haupt & Franklin Consulting & Civil Engineers
  - Haviland, Walter, 1897; 2 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Hawkeye Lightning Rod Company, 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
    Bert Beck
  - Hawkins, Gardner, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hawkins, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hawthorne, Julian, 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hayes, Henry R., 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
    Stone & Webster
  - Hays, Will S., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hazelwood, F. F., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hazlitt & Walker, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
    American Jeweler
  - H. & D. Press Clipping Bureau, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Heaphy, Musgrave, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Heath, Harry E., 1905-1907; 3 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Heaton, T. T., 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
    Steel Barrel Works
  - Heckscher, August, 1926; 2 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Hedges, Killingworth, 1893; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Heinze, J., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Heinze Electric, 1893-1894; 2 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Hele-Shaw, H. S., 1931; 2 items (Box Series I-20)
  - "Helen", 1935; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hempstead, Ernest A., 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hencky, H., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Henderson, F. C. & Company, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Henderson, Yandell, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
    Yale University. Laboratory of Applied Physiology
  - Hendricks, R. J., 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Henry, L., 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Henshaw, Frederick V., 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hensley, O. L., 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hepburn, Joseph S., 1918-1932; 10 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Hearld, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
    Folsom, de F.
  - Herbert, George C. & Company, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Herdman, W. A., 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
    The Royal Society
  - Herdman, William J., 1894; 3 items (Box Series I-20)
    Univ. of Michigan. Dept. of Medicine and Surgery. Electro-Theropeutical Laboratory
  - Herdt, L. A., 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
    McGill Univ. Dept. of Elec. Engineering
  - Hering, Carl, 1891-1924; 16 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Hering, Herman S., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Herrick, Charles H., [1894]-1932; 3 items (Box Series I-20)
  - Herringshaw's American Blue Book of Biography, [1922]; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hesketh, John, 1904; 3 items (Box Series I-20)
    Australia. Postmaster General's Dept.
  - Hess-Bright Manufacturing Company, 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-20)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1891- Aug. 1899; 16 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George, Sept.-Dec. 1899; 29 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jan.-Mar. 1900; 25 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Apr.-Jun. 1900; 27 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jul.-Sept. 1900; 29 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Oct.-Dec. 1900; 31 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jan.-Jun. 1901; 29 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jul.-Dec. 1901; 34 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jan.-Jun. 1902; 27 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jul.-Aug. 1902; 20 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Sept.-Dec. 1902; 22 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jan.-May 1903; 13 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jul.-Dec. 1903; 25 items (Box Series I-21)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jan.- Jul. 1904; 30 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., Aug.- Dec. 1904; 31 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1905; 34 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1906; 40 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1907; 18 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1908; 20 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1909; 18 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jan.-Jun. 1910; 25 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jul.- Dec 1910; 26 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1911; 25 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jan.- May 1912; 15 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jun.- Dec. 1912; 16 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1912; 26 items (Box Series I-22)
    Misc. Correspondence, incomplete
  - Hewitt, George W., 1913; 33 items (Box Series I-22)
  - Hewitt, George W., Jan.-Aug. 1914; 31 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hewitt, George W., Sept.-Dec. 1914; 23 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1915; 19 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hewitt, George W., 1916; 3 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hewitt, Isabel R., 1926-1935; 6 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hewitt, T. E., 1927; 4 items (Box Series I-23)
    Mayor of Southwark, England
  - Hewlett, E. M., 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Dunham Laboratory of Elec. Engineering
  - Heyl, Henry R., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hiern, F. B., 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Higel, Otto Company, Inc., 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Edward P. Mason
  - Higgan, Edward E., 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Success Magazine
  - Higginson, Henry L., 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - High School. Swampscott, Massachusetts, 1920-1929; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Highway Commission, 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Auto accident report
  - Highway Safety League, 1912; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hill, David Jayne, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hill, J. M., 1898; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hillhouse High School. Department of Physics, 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
    M. M. Marble
  - Hilliard, Martha E., 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hilma, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Elihu's neice
  - Himes, Charles F., 1896; 3 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hinkley, R. H. & Company, [1919]; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Book of Knowledge
  - Hirsh, Harry B., 1911-1930; 4 items (Box Series I-23)
  - History of Science Society, 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    F. E. Brasch
  - Hitchcock, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hobart, Henry M., 1906-1934; 10 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hobson, Arthur L., 1934; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hocker, W. F., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Haverstraw Electric Light
  - Hodgdon, Cashman & Company, 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hodges, N. D. C., 1891-1898; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hodgkins & Hodgkins, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hoereth, Otto, 1894; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hoffman, Leonard, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hofman, F. E., 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Holden, Frank, 1895-1936; 9 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Holland, H. T., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Holland, Thomas, 1904; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hollingsworth & Fraley, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Jos. C. Fraley
  - Holman, Silas W., 1887-1899; 5 items (Box Series I-23)
    M.I.T. Rodgers Laboratory of Physics
  - Holmes, C. F., 1906-1908; 4 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Holsinger, S. J., 1911; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Holtzer, Charles W., 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    Holtzer Cabot Electric Company
  - Home Library Association, 1891-1898; 4 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hooper, William L., 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hoover for President. Engineers National Committee, 1928; 4 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hope Club, 1896; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hopkins, Henry, 1896-1905; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hopkins, N. Monroe, 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hopkins, William J., 1892 (Box Series I-23)
  - Hopping, S. V., 1898; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Horlicks Malted Milk Company, 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Horn, Fred R. Bruce, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Horseless Age, 1896-1907; 5 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Horton, B. H., Mrs., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Horton, H. L. & Company, 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hoskins, William H., 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hosmer, W. B., 1899-1907; 6 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hotel Iroquois, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hotel Knickerbocker, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hotel Manhatten, 1901-1904; 4 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hotel Walton, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hotels Statler Co., Inc., 1923; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
    E. M. Statler
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, [1909]; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Houston, Edwin J., 1881-1899; 25 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Houston, Edwin J., 1902-1913; 26 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Howard, L. O., 1901; 5 items (Box Series I-23)
    Am. Assoc. for the Advancement of Science
  - Howe, Henry M., 1892-1900; 4 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Howe, William H., 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Howell, John W., 1909-1912; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hoyt, W. M., 1896-1898; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hubbell, J. E., 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hubbell, Joseph G., 1893; 4 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hudson, John E., 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Huey, William G., 1908; 2 items (Box Series I-23)
  - Hughes & Morris, Inc., 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Hull, G. F., 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-23)
  - Humphery, S. K., 1898; 3 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Humphreys, W. J., 1904; 3 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Hunt, Alfred E., 1898; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
    Pittsburg Reduction Co.
  - Hutchinson, M. R., 1904-1931; 4 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Hutchison, R., 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Hutton, F. R., 1892-1909; 4 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Hutton, R. S., 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
  - Hyde, Edward P., 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
  - Ice Cream Trade Journal, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
  - Iles, George, 1898-1908; 10 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Illmer, Louis, Jr., 1905-1915; 5 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Illuminating Engineer, 1907-1909; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Illuminating Engineering Society, 1908-1926; 37 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Illuminating Engineering Society. New England Section, 1907-1931; 10 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Illuminating Engineering Society. Science Advisory Committee, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
    J. W. Lapointe
  - Illuminating World, 1906; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Illustrated American Magazine, 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
    Lionel Stagge
  - Illustrated Press Bureau, 1913; 4 items (Box Series I-24)
  - India Wharf Brewing Company, 1892; 3 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Indian Journal of Physics, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
    C. V. Raman
  - Industrial Education Conference, 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
  - Industrial and Engineering Chemistry, 1926-1927; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
    H. E. Howe
  - Industrial Finance Company, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
  - Industrial Press, 1903-1906; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Industrial Securities Company, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
  - Ingalls, Jerome, 1888-1905; 3 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Institut Electro-Technique Montefiore, 1893-1904; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
    Eric Eurand
  - Institute Pasteur, 1890-1889; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Institute of Radio Engineers, 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
    Emil Simon
  - Institute of Technology, 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
    Historic Memorials Committee
  - Institution of Civil Engineers, 1889-1912; 36 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Institution of Civil Engineers, 1914-1932; 30 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Institution of Electrical Engineers, 1898-1932; 35 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Institution of Engineering Inspection, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
    C. J. Wharton
  - Institution of Mechanical Engineers, 1924; 4 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Institution of Structural Engineers, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
    M. G. Kiddy
  - Insull, Samuel, 1907-1931; 6 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Insurance Press, 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-24)
  - Insurance Society of New York, 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-24)
    E. R. Hardy
  - International Association of Electrical Inspectors, 1928-1933; 12 items (Box Series I-25)
  - International Astronomical Union, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    Adelaide Ames
  - International Commission on Illumination, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    G. H. Stickney
  - International Congress of Applied Chemistry, 1911-1912; 3 items (Box Series I-25)
    Bernhard Hesse
  - International Congress of Arts and Science, 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
  - International Electrical Congress, 1892-1903; 41 items (Box Series I-25)
  - International Electrical Congress, Jan.-Jun. 1904; 34 items (Box Series I-25)
  - International Electrical Congress, Jul. 1904-1913; 25 items (Box Series I-25)
  - International Electrotechnical Commission, 1911-1935; 28 items (Box Series I-25)
  - International Engineering Congress, 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    J. D. Cormack
  - International Illumination Congress, 1928; 3 items (Box Series I-25)
  - International Press Clipping Bureau, 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
  - International Radio Corporation, 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    J. E. Callahan
  - International Textbook Company, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    T. J. Foster
  - International Trade Press, Inc., 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    Charles Price
  - International Union for Cooperation in Solar Research, 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
  - Inventive Age, 1893-1895; 7 items (Box Series I-25)
  - Inventors' Protective Association, Inc., 1933; 2 items (Box Series I-25)
    Frank S. Williams
  - Inventors Publishing Company, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    M. Davis
  - Iowa City Gas and Electric Company, 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    George Carson
  - Iron Age, 1924-1932; 5 items (Box Series I-25)
  - Iron and Steel Institute, 1890; 2 items (Box Series I-25)
  - Island Improvement Society, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
  - Italian Electrotechnical Committee, 1910-1927; 3 items (Box Series I-25)
    Guido Semenza
  - Italian War Relief Fund of America, 1919; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    Robert U. Johnson
  - Iver Johnson Sporting Goods Company, 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
  - Ives, C. Q., 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    Widger & Miller Company
  - Ives, F. E., 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-25)
    Ives Process Company
  - Ives, Herbert E., 1919-1924; 4 items (Box Series I-25)
  - Ivins, Charlotte B. (Mrs. Ellwood), 1936; 2 items (Box Series I-25)
  - Ivins, Ellwood, 1902-1934; 23 items (Box Series I-25)
  - Jackson, [A. W.], 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
  - Jackson, Dugald C., 1904-1908; 29 items (Box Series I-25)
  - Jackson, Dugald C., 1909-1939; 24 items (Box Series I-25)
  - Jackson, Dugald C., Jr., 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    Birth Announcement
  - Jackson, George A., 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
  - Jackson, John P., 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
    Convention of Engineers of PA
  - Jackson, William, 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-25)
  - Jaggar, T. A., Jr., 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    Massachusetts of Technology
  - James, Alfred, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - James, Arthur Curtiss, 1932; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - James, Edward J., 1906; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - James, John, Jr., 1892; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jamison, John, 1933; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Japan (a publication), 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    James Steele
  - Japan Society of Boston, 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Jeffcott, H. H., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Jefferson, Thomas High School. Hall of Living Leaders, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    Judith Meyers
  - Jeffries, Thomas J., 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Jenkins, J. H., 1901; 6 items (Box Series I-26)
    General Electric Company
  - Jenkins Laboratories, 1925-1928; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jenks, W. J.., 1899-1902; 28 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jenks, W. J., 1903-1910; 30 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jewelers Circular Publishing Company, 1897-1898; 4 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jewell, Edward, 1915-1917; 5 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jewett, F. B., 1923-1924; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Johannesburg Exhibition 1904-5, 1902; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
    Grand International Peace Exhibition of South Africa
  - Johannsen, N., 1919; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - John Fritz Medal Board of Award, 1916-1929; 11 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    School of Hygiene and Public Health
  - Johnson, Alba B., 1930; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnson, Benjamin Newhall, 1906; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnson Brothers Transfer Line, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnson, Charles S., 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnson, Clapp & Underwood, 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    Robert P. Clapp
  - Johnson, Frederick A., 1900; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
    Gold Extraction, Mining and Supply Co.
  - Johnson, Henry R., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnson, John F., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnson and Phillips, 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    Hughes, C. A.
  - Johnson- Wynne Company, 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnston, Edward P., 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnston, Gilbert K., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnston, J. C. M., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    The Hampstead Institute
  - Johnston-Lairs, N. J., 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnston, Thomas J., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    G. E. Executive Correspondence
  - Johnston, Thomas J., 1906-1912; 6 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Johnston, William W., 1892-1896; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Joint Committee on Resuscitation from Electrical Shock, 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Jones, Bassett, 1918-1924; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jones, Daniel Fiske, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Jones, Edwin C., 1915; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jones, John Price, 1929; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jones Philip Mills, 1898; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
    Univ. of Calif. Medical Department
  - Jones Speedometer, 1906; 4 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Jones, William S., 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Jordan, A. L., 1913; 4 items (Box Series I-26)
    Polytechnic High School
  - Jordan, Edwin O., 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    Univ. of Chicago
  - Jordan, O. S., 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Jorquelleh Industrial Farm/ Liberia, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    S. O. Longemoh
  - Journal of Calendar Reform, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    Carl Liddle
  - Journal of Good Lighting, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    L. Garter
  - Journal of Industrial and Engineering Chemistry, 1921; 2 items (Box Series I-26)
    Charles H. Herty
  - Journal of Infectious Disease, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Journal of the Optical Society of American and Review of Scientific Instruments, 1922-1926; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
    F. K. Richtmeyer
  - Journal of Physical Therapeutics, 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    Margaret A. Cleaves
  - Journal of the United States Artillery, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
  - Jovian Order, 1914-1916; 3 items (Box Series I-26)
  - Joy, William M., 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-26)
    San Juan Light and Transit Company
  - Kaplan, Sisters M. & R., 1931-1932; 3 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kapp, Gisbert, 1893; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kassabian, Mihran K., 1901-1905; 5 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kasson, C. L., 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - "Kate", 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Keen, W. W., 1916-1927; 9 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Keenan, S. M., 1897-1915; 21 items (Box Series I-27)
    Wayne Co.,Mich. Superintendents of the Poor
  - Keily William E., 1900-1918; 14 items (Box Series I-27)
    Western Electrician
  - Kelley, James T., 1915; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
    Swampscott Library Cost Est.
  - Kelley, James Templeton, [1927]; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kellogg, Emily Stuart, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kellogg, Fred N., 1899-1900; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kells, C. Edmund, Jr., 1889; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kelly, Eula L., 1925-1926; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kelly, John F., 1902-1905; 4 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kelvin Centenary Committee, 1924; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
    D. N. Dunlop
  - Kelvin Medal Committee, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kelvin, Right Honorable Lord, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kemper, Ludwig, 1912; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
    Northwestern Electrical Exposition
  - Kennelly, Arthur E., 1898-1903; 32 items (Box Series I-7)
  - Kennelly, Arthur E., 1904-1908; 40 items (Box Series I-27)
    A. I. E. E.
  - Kennelly, Arthur E., 1909-1935; 34 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kent, Norton A., 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kerr, Thomas B., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Key, W. S., 1896; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Keyes, Frederick G., 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
    M.I.T.- Dept. of Chemistry
  - Keystone View Company, Inc., 1924-1929; 5 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Khan, Bahman H., 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kibbs, A. B., 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kidder, Peabody & Company, 1898-1905; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Killian, Daniel, 1891; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kimball, F. M., 1899-1929; 5 items (Box Series I-27)
  - King, Agnes Gardner, 1924-1925; 5 items (Box Series I-27)
  - King, Edward Skinner, 1928; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - King, Ellen A., 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - King, Moses, Jr., 1909; 5 items (Box Series I-27)
    Publisher of "Great Electricians"
  - King, William Harvey, 1901; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kinkead, William L., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kinraide, T. B., 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kinsley, Carl, 1898-1903; 4 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kinsley, Herbert E., 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kintner, S. M., 1913-1923; 3 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kirkland, Frank S., 1906-1908; 3 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kirkland, J. W., 1924; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kitsil, J., 1892; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kleeberg, Felix, 1895-1917; 5 items (Box Series I-27)
    Letter of recommendation from E. T.
  - Klein, W. W., 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kline, Frank W., 1893; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Klyce, S., 1920-1932; 14 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Knickerbocker Trust Company, 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Knight, T. S., 1927; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Knight, Walter H., 1898; 3 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Knoll, Lloyd M., 1922; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
    Central High School. Engineering Society
  - Knopp, Otto, 1903; 3 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Knowlen, J. Furniss, 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Knudson, Adolphus A., 1904-1905; 5 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Komakowsky, A. M., 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kraemeg, J. Adam, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Krause, Robert, 1896; 2 items (Box Series I-27)
  - Kuechler, Edward G., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
  - Kuntz, George F., 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-27)
    Pan American Exposition 1901
  - Kunz, Wheeler & Moffett Company, 1 item (Box Series I-27)
    Partial letter
  - Lafferty, George C., 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-28)